export const PROBLEM_OF_MONTH_2022 = [
    {
        month: "January",
        year: 2022,
        question: "2112q.pdf",
        solution: "2201a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Şevket Onur Yilmaz", affiliation: "Kabataş Erkek Lisesi" },
            { name: "Gurt Dovletov", affiliation: "The State Energy Instıtute of Türkmenistan" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Ankara" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "İsmail Toy", affiliation: "TOBB ETÜ, Ankara" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Lujain Qazmanny", affiliation: "Jordan" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Ahmet Yüksel", affiliation: "Aydın" },
            { name: "Deniz Can Karaçelebi", affiliation: "Çiçekliköy 50. Yıl Fen ve Teknoloji Lisesi" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "February",
        year: 2022,
        question: "2201q.pdf",
        solution: "2202a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Deniz Can Karaçelebi", affiliation: "Çiçekliköy 50. Yıl Fen ve Teknoloji Lisesi" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "March",
        year: 2022,
        question: "2202q.pdf",
        solution: "2203a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Mustafa Burak Topal", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Gurt Dovletov", affiliation: "The State Energy Instıtute of Turkmenıstan" },
            { name: "Lujain Qazmanny", affiliation: "Jordan" },
            { name: "Cüneyd Öztürk", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Alper Balcı", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Mehmet Koca", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Mümtaz Ulaş Keskin", affiliation: "Erciyes University" },
            { name: "Adem Limani", affiliation: "Lund University, Sweden" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Deniz Can Karaçelebi", affiliation: "Çiçekliköy 50. Yıl Fen ve Teknoloji Lisesi" },
            { name: "Lim Chang Kiat", affiliation: "Singapore" },
            { name: "Ritwik Chaudhuri", affiliation: "" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "April",
        year: 2022,
        question: "2203q.pdf",
        solution: "2204a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Şevket Onur Yilmaz", affiliation: "Kabataş Erkek Lisesi" },
            { name: "Mustafa Burak Topal", affiliation: "" },
            { name: "Lujain Qazmanny", affiliation: "Jordan" },
            { name: "Deniz Can Karaçelebi", affiliation: "Çiçekliköy 50. Yıl Fen ve Teknoloji Lisesi" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "May",
        year: 2022,
        question: "2204q.pdf",
        solution: "2205a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Cüneyd Öztürk", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Hasan Zübeyr Demir", affiliation: "Ankara" },
            { name: "Ahmet Yüksel", affiliation: "Aydın" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Altuğ Beyhan", affiliation: "YÖK TEBİP" },
            { name: "Selim Halykov", affiliation: "Saparmurat Turkmenbashy Specialized Comprehensive School" },
            { name: "Emirhan Delen", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Deniz Can Karaçelebi", affiliation: "Çiçekliköy 50. Yıl Fen ve Teknoloji Lisesi" },
            { name: "Alper Balcı", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Gürkan Koray Akpınar", affiliation: "" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Batyr Ovezmyradov", affiliation: "Saparmurat Turkmenbashy Specialized Comprehensive School" },
            { name: "Mustafa Burak Topal", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Mustafa Akdağ", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Alp Eren Köken", affiliation: "Antalya Yusuf Ziya Öner Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Choi Min Kyu", affiliation: "South Korea" },
            { name: "İsmail Özer", affiliation: "" },
            { name: "Malikşa Meylismyradow", affiliation: "" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "June",
        year: 2022,
        question: "2205q.pdf",
        solution: "2206a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Haruhisa Oda", affiliation: "Tokyo, Japan" },
            { name: "Selim Halykov", affiliation: "Saparmurat Turkmenbashy Specialized Comprehensive School, Türkmenistan" },
            { name: "Mustafa Akdağ", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Mustafa Burak Topal", affiliation: "Istanbul" },
            { name: "Mümtaz Ulaş Keskin", affiliation: "Erciyes University" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "July-August",
        year: 2022,
        question: "2206q.pdf",
        solution: "2207a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Choi Min Kyu", affiliation: "South Korea" },
            { name: "Mümtaz Ulaş Keskin", affiliation: "Erciyes University" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Mustafa Burak Topal", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University" },
            { name: "Deniz Can Karaçelebi", affiliation: "Çiçekliköy 50. Yıl Fen ve Teknoloji Lisesi" },
            { name: "Cüneyd Öztürk", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
            { name: "Paolo Perfetti", affiliation: "Universite degli studi di Tor Vergata Roma, Italy" },
            { name: "Deniz Cemal Yılmazsoy", affiliation: "" },
            { name: "Çınar Eren Arslan", affiliation: "Koç University" },
            { name: "Haruhisa Oda", affiliation: "Tokyo, Japan" },
            { name: "Alex Chiu", affiliation: "United Kingdom" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Selim Halykov", affiliation: "Saparmurat Turkmenbashy Specialized Comprehensive School, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Çağan Herek", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Hüseyin Ege Olcay", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Jurgen Weith", affiliation: "University of Applied Sciences Wurzburg-Schweinfurt, Germany" },
            { name: "Muhammetmyrat Gochmyradov", affiliation: "Turkmen State Instıtute of Architecture and Construction, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Abdulkadir Tanrıverdi", affiliation: "Eskişehir" },
            { name: "Salih Yavuz Yaman", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Semih Zaman", affiliation: "Sabancı University" },
            { name: "Alp Eren Köken", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Mehmet Özgün Cihangir", affiliation: "METU" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "September",
        year: 2022,
        question: "2207q.pdf",
        solution: "2209a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Mehmet Sarak", affiliation: "İstanbul Bahçeşehir Fen ve Teknoloji Lisesi" },
            { name: "Mahmut Sait Okyay", affiliation: "University of California Riverside, USA" },
            { name: "Seung-Ri Park", affiliation: "South Korea" },
            { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
            { name: "Choi Min Kyu", affiliation: "South Korea" },
            { name: "Cüneyd Öztürk", affiliation: "Northwestern University, USA" },
            { name: "Haruhisa Oda", affiliation: "Tokyo, Japan" },
            { name: "Altuğ Beyhan", affiliation: "YÖK TEBİP" },
            { name: "Richard Blatirmor", affiliation: "Spain" },
            { name: "Murat Apaydın", affiliation: "Bilkent alumnus" },
            { name: "Hasan Zübeyr Demir", affiliation: "Ankara" },
            { name: "Ece Özüduru", affiliation: "Urla, İzmir" },
            { name: "Tan Özalp", affiliation: "METU" },
            { name: "Kipp Johnson", affiliation: "Valley Catholic School, Beaverton, Oregon, USA" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "M. Anıl Taş", affiliation: "Frankfurt, Germany" },
            { name: "Abdulkadir Tanrıverdi", affiliation: "Eskişehir" },
            { name: "Mustafa Burak Topal", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Serdar Hojayev", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Ananda Raidu", affiliation: "Bangalore, India" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "October",
        year: 2022,
        question: "2209q.pdf",
        solution: "2210a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Mehmet Sarak", affiliation: "İstanbul Bahçeşehir Fen ve Teknoloji Lisesi" },
            { name: "Serdar Hojayev", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Mustafa Burak Topal", affiliation: "İstanbul" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "November",
        year: 2022,
        question: "2210q.pdf",
        solution: "2211a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Mustafa Burak Topal", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Haruhisa Oda", affiliation: "Tokyo, Japan" },
            { name: "Choi Min Kyu", affiliation: "South Korea" },
            { name: "Serdar Hojayev", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "December",
        year: 2022,
        question: "2211q.pdf",
        solution: "2212a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Choi Min Kyu", affiliation: "South Korea" },
            { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Özgür Soysal", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Mustafa Burak Topal", affiliation: "Istanbul" },
            { name: "Hüseyin Ege Olcay", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Güneş Parlakgül", affiliation: "Harvard University, USA" }
        ]
    }
];
